CHUCK: On April 21st. 1967.
the hundred-millionth GM vehicle
rolled off the line at
the plant in Janesville.
Three days later. another
car rolled off that same line.
This 1967 Chevrolet Impala
would turn out to be
the most important object
- in pretty much the whole universe.
- Whoo!
DEAN: Listen to her purr.
- This is the car you want.
- Oh. yeah?
You... You know
something about cars?
My dad taught me
everything about cars.
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (HORN HONKING)
I know it's been a long time.
Dean and I... We've... We've been through
a lot of bad. But this is different.
This is my fault and I
don't know how to fix it.
We need your help. God.
We need to know there's hope.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(TRAIN ENGINE CHUGGING)
(TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
SAM: Hey. DEAN: Hey.
SAM: Dude. what's
up with the shorts?
- DEAN: It's a free bunker.
- (SAM SCOFFS)
DEAN: Did you find
anything? SAM: Uh...
SAM: Not on The Darkness.
No. (GRUNTS)
DEAN: What about Metatron?
SAM: Still in the
wind. No leads.
DEAN: Great.
So. we have an ancient
evil out there somewhere.
just getting
stronger by the day.
Cass is getting
better. so there's that.
- Still wants to fix your. uh...
- I'm fine.
Fine. 100%.
All right. well. he's not. He
still needs more time to heal.
Well... (GRUNTS) Guess we
got nothing to do but get better.
I don't know about you. but
I've got some serious cabin fever.
I've washed every
car in here twice.
Well. I may have
found us a case.
- I mean. it's thin...
- Hey. thin works.
Tell me on the way.
Figures.
All right. let's hear
it. What do you got?
Okay. uh. Quaker Valley.
Oregon. town outside of Eugene.
Dwayne Markham. the local sheriff.
was found in the woods a couple days ago.
His body was mauled. so they
chalked it up to an animal attack.
- but I'm thinking...
- Werewolf.
- Yeah. maybe.
- Yeah. you're right. That is thin.
Yeah. Probably nothing. right?
Probably not.
Oregon. here we come.
What is that?
It's a smoothie.
Where's the beer?
Under the smoothies.
Where's the rest of the beer?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
- Ooh. it's Cass. We gotta. we gotta...
- Man.
I gotta get this.
Hey. Cass. Everything all right?
CASTIEL: Yeah. I'm fine.
I was just reading up about
the other cases in the
area that you're headed to.
I haven't found anything
yet that matches.
Cass. you've got one
job to do and that's to heal.
- You understand?
- CASTIEL: I can help.
Yeah. of course you can. Cass.
but. right now is the time for
you to focus on getting better.
This is just a milk run.
We got it. So. try and relax.
- CASTIEL: All right.
- Read a book.
Watch some Netflix.
- What's a "Netflix"?
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Go to my room. turn on
the TV. You'll figure it out.
All right.
Just call if you need anything.
Got it. Cass. Thanks.
You think he's gonna be okay?
He just needs some
time. you know? We all do.
Are you serious?
Dean. it's late. I'm exhausted
and. and... And starving.
And this place...
I mean. even Swayze wouldn't
come to this Roadhouse.
Okay. first of all. never
use Swayze's name in vain.
- Okay? Ever.
- (SCOFFS)
DEAN: Second. you
don't remember this place?
You don't remember Heather?
The hunter that we worked a
Wendigo case a couple years ago?
- Oh. yeah.
- Yeah. exactly.
What. she's here tonight?
I texted her. She's working
a rugaru case in Texas.
Actually. she never texted
me back. That's not the point.
The point is. is that we
have a ton of driving left to do
just to go to a town where
there's probably not a case.
But in there. good times.
And time heals all wounds.
Sam. especially good times.
What do you say?
I say. knock yourself out.
I'm gonna find a diner. dig
into the lore like Cass did.
see if anything's ever
happened where we're headed.
Oh. man. you really gotta
learn how to have fun.
Seriously. it's pathetic.
(BLUES SONG PLAYING)
(SAM GROANS)
Mistakes were made. Mmm-hmm.
Who are you?
- Oh.
- SAM: Uh. good morning.
SAM: (CLEARS THROAT)
That's. uh. my brother Dean.
Sorry. Sam. I didn't. I didn't
realize you had company.
SAM: Yeah. Yeah. could
you give us a minute?
Hi.
Well. I'll just. uh... Just
won't be here anymore.
So. you kids take your time.
Have you seen my hairpin?
- Dean. I can explain what was going on...
- No. no. no. No.
(NIGHT MOVES PLAYING)
- Don't Night Moves me.
- Shh.
Just let it wash over you.
- Look...
- Just take it in.
(SAM CHUCKLES)
(MOUTHING LYRICS)
This is ridiculous.
One of the greatest rock
writers of all time. Samuel.
It's Sam.
(SINGING)
You started this.
Here we go. Come on now.
(BOTH SINGING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Next time. I choose.
- Hey.
- Hands off the wheel.
You're not even
looking at the road.
"Digging into the lore."
Is that what the kids
are calling it these days?
(SAM CHUCKLES)
Man. I needed that.
(DEAN CHUCKLES)
And hey. look at that. you're
finally not a virgin anymore.
But you know what?
I think it was time.
- I respect the fact that you. uh...
- (CHUCKLES)
You know. you wanted to
stay true and pure and waited.
Yeah. you know
what? You're an idiot.
Even put a blanket down.
Buddy. classy and
thoughtful as always.
I tried to give her my number.
You know what she said?
"We got tonight. Who
needs tomorrow?"
Is everything a Bob
Seger song to you?
Yes.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Well... (SIGHS) It was
nice knowing you. Piper.
Piper?
(LAUGHS) That's awesome.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
- Heather. One-night wonders. man.
Shoot. we're lucky
we still get that at all.
Really? You don't ever
want something more?
I'm sorry. have you met us?
We're batting a whopping zero
in domestic life. man. Goose eggs.
You don't ever think about
something? Not marriage or whatever.
But. something. you know. with a hunter?
Somebody who understands the life?
Have you not heard a single
word Bob's been singing about?
You're tired. I can
tell. You're exhausted.
Well. I'm still wired. so I'm
gonna pull over. get some gas.
You hop in the back. get some
Z's. 'cause. buddy. you earned 'em.
Proud of you! Piper.
Mmm. Man. she smelled good. too.
(SOMEDAY SOON
PLAYING ON THE STEREO)
(YAWNS)
What are you listening to?
JOHN: Your mom
used to love this song.
SAM: Dad?
You okay. pal? You
look a little spooked.
It's nice to be back
behind the wheel.
Looks like Dean's taken
good care of this old beast.
Seems like he's taken
good care of you. too.
What is this? Another vision?
Are you having visions. son?
Don't call me that.
- What? A father can't call his...
- No. my father is dead.
When has death ever
stopped a Winchester?
Look. I don't know
what this is. but...
What you said about relationships.
wanting something more...
I never wanted this for
you boys. this life. Not really.
We turned out okay.
(CHUCKLES) You did. didn't you?
But that was on you
boys. You did that. not me.
Well. you played your
part. (CHUCKLES)
I did my best. anyway.
for what it was worth.
This isn't real.
I never could fool you. could I?
I prayed when I
was in that church.
And I saw something.
And now. here you are. whoever
you are. whatever you are.
What the hell is this?
Dream.
Vision. Call it what you want.
The message is still the same.
The Darkness is coming.
Only you boys can stop it.
SAM: Okay. fine.
How?
We need help. not
visions of dead people.
God helps those
who help themselves.
Who are you?
(HORN HONKING)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Welcome to the Winchester Motel.
We don't have cable. but
we do have room service.
You were singing in your sleep.
That song Mom loved. Dad
used to always play for us.
I think I've actually
still got the tape.
Hey. Dean. um...
You said when you saw The Darkness.
you weren't sure whether it was. uh...
The real thing
or a vision. right?
Mmm-hmm.
I think I've been having
visions. too. lately.
I mean. it's just images. I
mean. more of a feeling. really.
But I just had one right now.
and. and Dad was in it.
But it wasn't Dad like. like.
the Dad that. that I grew up with.
It was Dad when he was our age.
And I guess it wasn't
even really Dad.
It was someone
pretending to be Dad and...
Okay. what makes you say that?
For starters. he told me
everything I wanted to hear.
- Yeah. doesn't sound like Dad.
- No.
Anyways. whoever it was.
they had a message to deliver.
They said The
Darkness is coming.
And only you and I can stop it.
Did they happen to give you
any helpful tips on how to do that?
He said. "God helps those
who help themselves."
I mean. maybe these
visions are coming from God.
Whoa.
Pump the brakes.
I mean. Dean. the first
one happened after I prayed.
You prayed? When was this?
Back in the hospital.
Why?
Because I was infected.
I was infected. I'm not anymore.
And I. I never went full rabid.
You get infected and
you didn't even tell me.
- Dean...
- What did you pray about?
I guess I was just looking
for answers. you know?
Well. I'm sure whatever is kicking
around in your head right now
is a side effect from the infection
that you failed to tell me about.
You know. I don't
think it's that simple.
Come on. man. That quote?
"God helps those who help
themselves"? God didn't say that.
That's not even in the Bible.
That's an old proverb that
dates way back to Aesop.
I read.
And more importantly.
when was the last time
God answered any
one of our prayers?
It's not a vision. Sam. All right?
It's just some... Some fever dream.
That's all.
And as far as Dad goes. I
dream about Dad all the time.
- You do?
- Of course I do.
It's usually the same one. too.
We're all in the car. I'm
sitting in the driver's seat.
Dad's sitting shotgun. But
there aren't any shotguns.
There's no monsters. There's
no hunting. There's none of that.
It's just...
He's teaching me how to drive.
And. uh... And I'm not little like I was
when he actually taught me how to drive.
I'm 16. and he's helping
me get my learner's permit.
Of course. you're in the backseat.
just begging to take a turn.
We pull up to the
house. the family house.
And I park in the driveway.
and he looks over and he says.
"Perfect landing. son."
I have that dream every couple of
months. It's kind of comforting. actually.
I always. uh...
(CHUCKLES)
I always dream about Mom.
Usually the same
kind of thing. though.
- Normal life?
- Yeah. Normal life.
But. Dean. this wasn't
just a dream. I'm telling you.
Why would somebody dress up
like Dad to give you a message?
I mean. Dad.
You don't exactly have a history
of listening to what he had to say.
But you said The Darkness
is sending messages to you.
Maybe whatever is the opposite of The
Darkness is sending messages to me.
And you think that
this thing is God?
Come on. How many. how many opportunities
has God had to crack this piñata.
and I don't see any
candy on the floor. do you?
Okay. then maybe
it's not God. but...
(SIGHS)
I know what you're
trying to do here.
You're trying to find some.
some greater meaning to it all.
Right? Some fate
to what went down.
But I'm telling you. Sam.
The Darkness? It's on us.
And no one's gonna
help us. certainly not God.
so. we'll have to figure this
thing out. like we always do.
But until then. we hunt.
This case. for starters.
Of course. this case is...
Which is probably nothing.
Yeah. probably nothing.
(SIGHS)
Good night. jerk.
(SMACKS LIPS)
Night. bitch.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTERING)
Hey. the coroner showed
me the sheriff's body.
And. uh. it was
mauled all right.
And get this. Heart missing.
body completely drained of blood.
So. what? We're looking at
a. a werewolf/vampire hybrid?
- Say it with me. a Were-pire.
- (SIRENS BLARING)
- (CHUCKLES)
- Huh?
No.
- Come on.
- I'm not saying that.
Whatever. I called Cass.
told him to look into the lore.
What do you got?
Right. well. uh. the sheriff's
replacement. Deputy Donnelly...
He's not the brightest bulb.
but I got a copy of his report.
Maybe he missed something.
DONNELLY: Agents.
DEAN: Deputy.
This must be your partner.
Agent Walsh. right?
Pleasure to meet you.
I just want to thank
you both for stoppin' by.
We really appreciate
your due diligence.
Oh. Actually. uh. do you know a
motel where we can crash for the night?
You're stayin'?
Yeah. just wanna
kick all the tires.
Well. uh. there's a motel on
Downey that'll give you a good price.
And if you're looking
for a decent meal.
you can't beat Aunt Mel's.
down by the train station.
Parking is a bitch. but it's the
best damn steak in the whole state.
You had me at "steak."
DEAN: (LAUGHS) All right.
Now we're cookin' with gas.
Valet?
You... What?
(CHUCKLES) Dean.
people valet park all the time.
Come on. live a little.
WOMAN: Welcome to Aunt Mel's.
- Home of the...
- Yeah. listen.
Jessie. not a scratch. okay?
(CHUCKLES)
Spider caught a fly.
I repeat. spider caught a fly.
(CHUCKLES)
- Let's go! Come on!
- JORDAN: Okay!
Hell. yeah. Let's
roll! (GIGGLES)
Let's get this party started.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Oh. my God!
(LAUGHING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yes. sir? We're on our way.
My way.
JORDAN: What did you do?
I'm gonna get fired.
JESSIE: Come on! JORDAN: Okay!
- I gotta go. Let's go!
- Where's my purse?
You probably just
left it in your car.
- What?
- I gotta go! I don't wanna get fired!
(GRUNTS)
Strong work.
Jessie. Strong work.
Thanks.
So. what's next?
I want. uh. to talk to
the sheriff's widow.
Lily Markham.
Maybe she knows something
about why her husband
was out in the woods
in the first place.
All right. well.
I'll drop you off.
I wanna go back to the woods
where they found the body.
Something wasn't right about
those crime scene photos.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(GRUNTS)
- Cass. you okay?
- CASTIEL: I'm mostly confused.
I'm not sure how orange correlates
with black in a way that's new.
Step away from the Netflix.
- Sorry.
- It's okay. We've all had a binge.
You find anything in the lore?
Well. there is a creature that
feeds on hearts and blood.
A Were-pire. you might say?
Come on. I know
you wanna say it.
In the lore. it's referred
to as a Whisper.
That's lame.
Silver will kill it. but you may
want to decapitate it just to be sure.
All right. sounds good.
I'm at the crime scene now.
It was staged. The body was dragged.
There were no signs of struggle.
Body was moved there to
look more like an animal attack?
Yeah. maybe. It was
pretty sloppy. though.
You. uh...
What else you got
on these things?
Listen to this. Whispers
have a fascinating history...
Hang on.
CASTIEL: Actually. they were once believed
to be in the bloodline of werewolves.
but in fact. they are
more similar to demons.
DEAN: Deputy? What's going on?
CASTIEL: They. uh... They got their
nickname from how quiet their attacks are.
- Because of their stealthiness...
- (TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
they've. uh. lived on
the fringes for centuries.
Although. there were several
that were hunted and killed
during the Salem witch...
Wait a minute. Okay.
according to this.
Whispers only feed
during a solar eclipse.
Uh. so. Dean.
I... I don't believe
- what you're hunting is a Whisper.
- (DONNELLY GRUNTING)
- Must be another creature of some kind.
- (DEAN GRUNTING)
Okay. Fine. I'll say it.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Maybe it is your
so-called Were-pire.
But to be honest. I have never
heard of a creature with that name.
- Dean. what is that?
- (GRUNTS)
Dean?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUN FIRES)
Dean. Dean. are you
all right? I hear gunshots.
- Dean!
- (DEAN GROANING)
Dean?
Dean!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ah. turns out I did
shoot the deputy.
- CASTIEL: Wait. Dean. is. is everything...
- The deputy was a Were-pire.
It's all right.
Silver bullets worked.
No. Dean. listen.
- (DONNELLY GROWLING)
- According to the lore. the timing is off.
The next solar eclipse in
North America is years away.
- It can't be a...
- Hang on.
Dean. wait.
- This thing couldn't be...
- (GRUNTING)
(DONNELLY GROWLING)
Dean?
(DONNELLY GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
Scratch that.
You gotta cut off their...
(GROWLING)
(DONNELLY CHOKING)
CASTIEL: Dean.
it's not a Whisper.
Yeah. I'm starting to get that.
Give me a sec.
(GRUNTS)
All right.
(DONNELLY GROWLING)
All right. that...
(GRUNTS)
(DONNELLY CONTINUES GROWLING)
(GROWLING STOPS)
(DEAN GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
Okay.
(DONNELLY GROWLING)
Smile. asshat.
- (DONNELLY GROWLING)
- (CAMERA CLICKING)
(SIGHS)
- All right. Cass. you there?
- CASTIEL: Of course. What's going on?
Well. whatever it is.
silver slows it down.
I. uh... I'm sending you a
picture right now of its fangs.
I've never seen
anything like it.
See if there's a match
in the lore. would you?
CASTIEL: I'm on it.
(SIGHS)
(LINE DIALING)
SAM: Dean. I got jumped.
- You okay?
- I think. for now.
Pretty sure we're
dealing with a pack here.
Uh. two of these things were
attacking Mrs. Markham when I arrived.
I. I filled them with silver.
but it only slowed them down.
Yeah. well. Deputy Dumbass
is one of them as well.
He's. uh... He's in two
pieces and still alive.
Where you at now?
Mrs. Markham was knocked
out. I carried her to a house nearby.
- Here. I'll text you the address now.
- All right. sit tight. I'm on my way.
(GRUNTS)
Buddy's gettin' jumped.
(SIGHS)
SAM: Door was open
when I got to the house.
By the time I searched through it.
they'd already beaten her unconscious.
Maybe she knew something
or something about what
happened to her husband.
So what. they tried to take her out
while the deputy went back to the scene?
Yeah. he went to
fix it up. Found me.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hey. Cass. tell me
you got something
- that doesn't involve chicks in prison.
- (CHUCKLES)
Bet you never thought
you'd say that out loud.
CASTIEL: It's a Nachzehrer.
- Come again?
- A ghoul and vampire-like creature.
A Ghoul-pire! Right?
Some breeds feed on
the flesh of the dead.
Others feed on the blood
and hearts of the living.
They run in small packs. but they
usually keep an extremely low profile.
Great. So. how do we kill 'em?
CASTIEL: Well.
they're already dead.
So in a manner of speaking. they just
need to be reminded that they're dead.
- You need a Charon's obol.
- Of course.
SAM: Yeah. in ancient
Greece. when a person died.
some people believed you had to
put an obol. or a coin in their mouth.
so they could use it as currency to be
taken across the river to the underworld.
CASTIEL: Right. you place a
coin in a Nachzehrer's mouth.
then sever their head.
and that will kill them.
And according to the lore.
if you kill the pack's Alpha.
everyone they've turned will
revert back to human form.
Awesome. All right.
where do we find an obol?
CASTIEL: Well. according
to the Men of Letters' records.
you're gonna need a copper coin.
They used to use pennies.
so. you'll need one of those.
Yeah. but one minted pre-1982.
So before 1982.
pennies were 95% copper.
Since then. they're
only copper-plated zinc.
- Wow. Your nerdiness knows no bounds.
- (SAM SCOFFS)
- You're welcome.
- DEAN: All right. well. thanks. Cass.
Good work. Way to
come off the bench.
CASTIEL: What bench?
Just get back to
getting better. okay?
Got nothing.
Well. yeah. I mean. who carries
pennies these days. anyway?
- I'll be right back.
- DEAN: Yeah.
Mrs. Markham?
- Mrs. Markham. It's okay.
- (GASPING)
I'm Dean Winchester.
- My brother Sam and...
- Where am I?
You were attacked by the same
people that killed your husband.
My husband.
DEAN: Now do you know something
about what happened to him?
Maybe that's why these
people attacked you?
Okay.
Well. we're gonna take you
someplace safe. all right?
And then we're gonna
kill these sons of bitches.
(MUFFLED GROWLING)
- (DONNELLY GROWLING LOUDLY)
- (GASPS)
Whoa. whoa. whoa. I could.
uh... I could explain that.
- Well. maybe not.
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Um. it's like the thing
that attacked you. okay?
(STUTTERS) It's a Ghoul-pire.
The point is. it can't
hurt you anymore.
- At least. I don't think it can. It's...
- (MUFFLED GROWLING)
You know what?
Let's just get rid of it.
(SHUDDERS)
Here we go.
Okay. all right.
See? There we go.
- You okay?
- Your family.
You do anything
for them. don't you?
DEAN: Absolutely.
Yeah. but not if it costs
too much. (CHUCKLES)
No.
You do everything for them.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Everything else is meaningless.
But I did it wrong.
Now I've ruined everything.
This isn't your fault.
I put my family at risk.
They were right to attack me.
But I know how to make it right.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Where is it? What did you
do with the maker's body?
You're gonna tell
me or I will end you!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- (GUN FIRES)
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
See? That wasn't so hard.
Now. I know what to do with you.
(LILY SINGING)
I can make this right
(DONNELLY GASPING)
LILY: You're okay!
See? I fixed it. You're okay.
DONNELLY: I know you're awake.
I know you're a hunter.
(SIGHS)
And I know you're a Nachzehrer.
(DONNELLY LAUGHS)
The maker. right?
The pack Alpha?
Well. maybe you're
not as dumb as you look.
Thought you and yours
like to keep a low profile.
Sadly. rookies like Lily
here aren't up to snuff
when it comes to
keeping their feeding quiet.
So. you killed your husband?
He wouldn't join us.
People who don't join are food.
But. I... I messed up. and
I... I didn't bury him right.
DONNELLY: It's my fault. really.
You weren't properly trained.
DONNELLY: (CHUCKLES) But
everyone deserves a mulligan. don't they?
That's all my people
were trying to do. Lily.
They weren't going to kill you.
Hell. I need you.
I need all the help I can get.
How many have you turned?
In the first 100 years? Three.
In the last month? Sixteen.
What. are you trying
to field a baseball team?
It's like I said. I need help.
every strong hand I can find.
And I need an army
to fight The Darkness.
Oh. it's comin'. for all of us.
There's nothing hunters or
any human can do about it.
Do you know how to stop it?
I don't think
anything can stop it.
I'm just tryin' to
buy some time.
so I'm turning as many strong
men and women as I can.
Your brother will make a fine
addition to the rank and file.
While you slept. I sent him a
text message from your phone.
Oh. he's heading
into a trap right now.
You'd make a good soldier. too.
But you cut off my head.
and I can't stand for that.
Don't worry.
I'm an "every part of
the buffalo" kind of guy.
Your death won't go to waste.
You'll be your
brother's first meal.
(DONNELLY LAUGHS)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- (LILY GASPS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CRASHING)
(DEAN GRUNTING)
(DONNELLY GROWLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(THUDDING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(LILY GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(DONNELLY GROWLING)
(DONNELLY GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHING)
Oh. baby. I'm so sorry.
(GROANING)
Oh. my God. What have I...
My kids.
My kids. They turned my
kids. They're with the others.
Please.
Sam.
Yeah. yeah.
(SIGHS)
(LILY SIGHS)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(GRUNTS)
- (ENGINE SPUTTERING)
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
(ENGINE DIES)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
- Come on. baby. Yeah! There we go.
- (ENGINE STARTING)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Ah.
Hang on.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
BOY: Mom!
(LILY LAUGHS)
- GIRL: You okay?
- Probably nothing. right?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
- DEAN: Everybody all right back there?
- Uh. yeah.
They all changed back.
(SIGHS)
So. it was Deputy Dumbass. huh?
(GRUNTS) Yeah. Deputy Dumbass.
You know. he was trying to build an army.
Yeah. I know. To
fight The Darkness.
Dean. even the
monsters are scared.
Well. let 'em be.
You and I. we're gonna
end this thing now.
You. you mind starting
tomorrow? (CHUCKLES)
- Deal.
- Deal. (CHUCKLES)
We'll get Cass to fix you up.
Only if he fixes you up. too.
Okay. Mom.
Let's go home.
You know what? We are home.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Come on. Come on.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- Ah.
There's my girl.
(NIGHT MOVES PLAYING)
English-SDH
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm